biofaces.com 2015-12-10

# Privacy Policy - Biofaces - Bring Nature Closer

**What is the privacy policy?**

Privacy Policy specifies the treatment given by BIOFACES to personal information provided by users of resources and services BIOFACES 

**Collected Information**

BIOFACES collects the following personal information as visitors register as new users: 

  * • Login (for access BIOFACES); 
  * • Password (for access BIOFACES); 
  * • And other 

**Use of information**

BIOFACES uses this information to: 

  * • Identify the users on the site (through login and password); 
  * • Presenting author's profile if you have content published on the site; 
  * • Determine how each section or service is accessed in order to improve services 

BIOFACES receives and automatically saves information about visitasdos users to the site on their servers, including IP address, cookiesde BIOFACES and pages accessed 

BIOFACES will not sell, share or rent information pessoaisdos users to third parties under any circumstances. However, BIOFACES reserves the right to provide this information in court aprocessos response or in the event of a suspected breach of BIOFACES

**Terms of Use**

**Use of Cookies**

Cookies are small files that usually contain an anonymous unique identifier, sent to users by BIOFACES earmazenados on your computer. BIOFACES uses cookies to identify and authenticate users when they access the site. Anonymous (not registered) users can also receive cookies so that BIOFACES can estimate the audience of the site 

Users can configure your browser to accept or reject all cookies or to notify you when a cookie is sent to them. How this is done in a different way by each browser, users must use their browsers to help parasaber how to modify their preferences on cookies. If users reject all cookies (not recommended), they will not be able to use the resources and BIOFACES services that require identification, such as sections for the publication of content. 

**How to view, update or delete personal information on BIOFACES**

Users and registered and was identified in the qualquermomento BIOFACES can view, update or delete your personal information through the "My Profile". If they want to completely delete any personal information about BIOFACES, users have to contact and request its cancellation BIOFACES registration 

**Information Security**

Users and subscribers information is protected by a password, for security and privacy reasons. That's why the BIOFACES password is individual and secret. BIOFACES never ask for your password via email or phone 

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

BIOFACES may change this privacy policy as it sees fit.   
So, users are recommended to visit this page.
